NYSUT Field Services Department Files. 6174/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Dean Streiff Files: Uniserv Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  Document, "A Proposal for a Unified Staff Service Program (UNISERV) to the Board of Directors of the New York State Teachers Association," May 1971; UniServ agreement between NEA and NYSTA; tentative UniServ clusters, effective only for 1972-73; loan authorization for organizing campaign by Legislative Conference of City University of New York (CUNY); September 22, 1971; signed draft of loan guarantee by NEA and NYSTA, September 22, 1971; budget for Legislative Conference of the City University, revised September 22, 1971; Memorandum of Agreement between NYSTA and NEA re costs associated with election campaign by Legislative Conference of CUNY, 1971; list of expenditures out of LC- CUNY operating budget for campaign, October 17, 1972; NYSTA memo re dues problem at LC-CUNY, April 20, 1972; remarks by Arnold Cantor at NYSTA Board meeting re dues problem at LC-CUNY, April 12-15, 1972
- Dean Streiff Files: Regional Offices-Staff Recruitment, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  Memo from Dean Streiff proposing a master plan of eight regions, February 6, 1969; map; organizational chart; memo re interest of individual staff members in regional assignments, April 15, 1969; related memos re potential candidates for field representative positions; memo to Streiff suggesting more prestigious title than Regional Office Coordinator, June 26, 1969; memo to Streiff from Robert I. Allen, noting dissatisfaction with current salary, requesting consideration for promotion to regional coordinator for Albany area, April 8, 1969
- Dean Streiff Files: NEA Constitution, 1973-1975 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  Constitution for NYSUT, n.d.; as amended through March 24, 1974; Constitution of the AFT, September 1973 and 1974; New Constitution and Bylaws of the National Education Association (effective as outlined in the transition calendar), adopted by the 1973 NEA Representative Assembly; Charter, Bylaws, and Rules of the National Education Association of the United States of America, July 1973; National Education Association Proposed Amendments to the Current Bylaws & Standing Rules and Proposed Amendments to the New Constitution & Bylaws 1974; letter to Tom Hobart from Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'Rith re filing charges of discrimination against NEA, March 25, 1974, with attached memo to NEA Board of Directors re lawsuit over ethnic minority guarantees in NEA's new constitution and bylaws, April 3, 1974; related correspondence re provisions of new NEA constitution
- United Teachers: Personnel Directory, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  List of board and staff by regional office, with photos
- NYSTA Legislative Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- NYSTA Newsletters: Staffline, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- NYSTA Newsletters: Guidelines, Hotline, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- NYSTA Constitution and Bylaws, 1913-1971 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  Booklets
- NYSUT Constitution, 1974-1981 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  Booklets, including merger agreement with United Teachers